came to the Buffalo Bills. What was your
interaction with them throughout the
pre-draft process?
>> Um, we had a uh a private workout and
also a private meeting. Um, you know, I
got to meet Coach Myers and his guys
very well. And, you know, it was just,
you know, actually, you know, BC guys up
there, uh, Kell Gearstein. So, you know,
me and him, you know, have a great
relationship and stuff like that. So,
I'm just I'm honestly ecstatic. I'm I'm
ready to roll. I'm ready to do this
thing. What do you know about Buffalo?
>> Not much, but I got got some family from
family up there. So, I be I be I be
good, man. I'm ready to roll.
>> All right, good. So, have you ever come
up to see your family? You ever been up
here before?
>> Yeah, a little bit. Yeah.
>> Okay. And uh, of course, what do you
think? What do you know about Bill's
Mafia? The fan base up here?
>> Electric. Electric, man. Bill's Mafia,
man. I love it. I love the energy they
bring. I love, you know, the the vibes,
man. You know, it's it's electric.
Do you um do you see yourself at tackle
or guard in the NFL? There's been some
projections for you for both.
>> I mean, wherever the team needs me,
that's that's honestly where where I'm
going to go. And, you know, I'm I'm
going to work my tail off, you know, try
to be the best I could be, but you know,
not to not to go into too depth into it.
Just wherever the team needs me.
>> Well, congratulations again, Jude. We'll
see you up here.
>> Yes, sir. I appreciate you, sir.
>> You got it.
Hey Jude, this is Katherine Fitzgerald
from the Buffalo News. How are you
doing?
>> I'm good, Catherine. How you feeling?
>> I'm good, thanks. Um, I just wanted to
follow up just on position versatility.
What makes you confident that you can
play wherever the team needs you?
>> Uh, really just my athletic ability, but
um, you know, I'm just, you know, my
mindset as well. Uh, I come in and work
every day and, you know, I just treat
every day like it's another opportunity
to get better. So, you know, I'm ready.
I'm ready to work for the Bills, man.
I'm ready to get get it started.
>> Where do you feel your game grew the
most last season?
>> Um, I probably say definitely in the run
game. Um, but overall, um, I think I
think I think I saw a lot of
improvements from the from the previous
year uh to last year. So,
>> and then are there any players that you
model your game after when you're
studying film or do you like pick from
different people or how does that work
for you? Uh definitely different people
because you know you can't just try to
emulate just off of one guy because that
guy is gonna be different from you in
every aspect. But you know I watch Larry
Tonsu, Trent Williams, uh Christian
Darasaw, a lot of those guys. Um you
know even even some Deion Dawkins like
you know I'm excited to get in the
building and work with him and Spencer
Brown. So I'm ready to work with those
guys get better each and every day.
>> Awesome. Thanks Jude. Congrats again.
>> Thank you so much. You have a good one.
>> Thanks.
Hi Jude. John Warl with the Associated
Press. Congratulations.
>> I appreciate it, John. Thank you.
>> Um, just what what was it like waiting
around until today and and having Well,
today being your your your weight ending
early today. What was that like over the
past, you know, couple of days? How did
you spend your time?
>> Uh, I just was here with the family. um
just you know enjoying enjoying the
company of my loved ones and and just
you know embracing the moment. I mean it
was you know it's tough to to you know
see your name fall and and stuff like
that but I mean you know God's plan is
God's plan and you know you can't defeat
it. So
>> and when you got the call um what was
that like?
>> I ain't going to lie to you John. I
cried cried a lot but that I was very
emotional but you know I I worked
towards this goal and you know I just
know that it's just the beginning and
I'm I'm happy the Buffalo Bills took a
chance on me and I'm just going to
continue to work my butt off and and try
to give the best I got each and every
day.
>> And you talked about, you know, knowing
Dion and and and a coach and what's it
like, you know, joining a team that has
Josh Allen?
>> Best quarterback in the in the NFL, man.
You know, shout out to Josh. I'm excited
to, you know, go to work with him each
and every day. Um, and just, you know,
feed off everybody's energy. I'm I'm
very excited for it.
>> Good stuff. Congrats.
>> Thank you, John. Appreciate you.
Still still can't. I'm sorry. I
apologize. Yeah.
>> We're gonna go to Matt.
>> Um, we're going to go to Matt now.
>> Hey Jude. Uh, congratulations Matt Pino
from Syracuse.com.
>> How you doing Matt?
>> I'm great. I'm great. Um, you obviously
played uh at tackle uh every game at
Boston College. During the draft
process, how much did teams in the Bills
specifically talk about, you know,
position flexibility and the ability to
maybe play guard in the NFL if asked
about and how do you how confident do
you feel if if you were to be asked to
do something like that?
>> I mean, you know, conversations go by.
You know, you definitely talk about it
and you you know, there's definitely a
chance for it. Um, I feel like I'm, you
know, I'm going to put my best foot
forward and, you know, work it out each
and every Hey, I know there's going to
be some high roads, some low roads, but
I just got to stay even kill when it
come down to it.
>> You mentioned uh the private workout
with the Bills. Uh Pat Meyers, uh the
new offensive line coach. What were your
impressions of him and the the staff and
and that workout?
>> I love Coach Pat, man. I mean, coach
Coach Myers, he he had great energy, him
and his staff. Um you know, even in the
meeting room, it was, you know, it was a
good vibe. He was teaching me some of
his stuff and, you know, I'm just ready
to learn from him and ready to, you
know, give him my best each and every
day.
Um, have you watched uh a lot of Deion
Dawkins tape at any point during college
or?
>> Yeah, for sure. Yeah, him and him and
Spencer Brown for sure. I mean, you if
you want to, you know, be the best and
be around the best, you got to kind of
watch and just take some stuff that they
put into it. So,
>> awesome stuff. Thanks, man. I appreciate
you.
>> Yes, sir. Appreciate you. Have a good
one.
Me now.
>> Yes, sir.
All right. Thank you for my guy Sal
Kapacho with that assist right there.
But uh Big Jude uh just care to talk
about uh how does it feel to join the
contender right away?
>> Man, it's a blessing, man. All glory to
God, man. Thank you, Jesus, for
everything. Honestly, I'm I'm ready to
roll, man. I'm excited.
>> Um just um just care to talk about your
style of play.
>> Um definitely a lot of athleticism, a
lot of range. Um, but you definitely
would get some dog and some nastiness
from me for sure.
>> Absolutely. That word nastiness is uh
out of the out all three picks.
Everybody's keep saying that word. So,
um um I just care to talk about your
process, right? Um Coach Magic uh he's a
real good friend of mine back there in
St. Francis and I just care to talk
about the process from going from St.
Francis to Boston College now to the
pros. Uh, I mean, you know, wasn't
really a highly recruited guy coming out
of high school. Um, went to, you know,
the best high school in the country. Um,
you know, I ended up going to Boston
College because I felt like, you know,
it had a good, uh, both sides of the
story. I got I got to be able to get my
degree and, you know, be able to go get
it from a big university, a good
university, but also, you know, get
achieve my dream of going to the NFL.
So, I thought it was a I thought it was
the best opportunity for me to, you
know, maximize my life and maximize my
my my future to say. Um, so I'm just,
you know, I'm excited now, you know,
just got drafted and I'm I'm ready to
roll.
>> All right. So, yeah, send a shout out to
your coaches out there in St. Francis
cuz shout out all the guys, man. Shout
out everybody.
>> Yeah, you got a handful of guys in this
year's drag class. But, uh, man,
congratulations and, uh, I'll see you
soon.
>> Yes, sir. Appreciate you.